const questions = [
       {
      question: 'What is the primary purpose of CSS in web development?',
      options: ['To create web pages','To style web pages','To store data','To program web applications'],
      answer: 'To style web pages',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a valid way to integrate CSS into a webpage?',
      options: ['Inline','External','Internal','All of the above'],
      answer: 'All of the above',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which CSS property is used to change the text color of an element?',
      options: ['text-color','color','font-color','background-color'],
      answer: 'color',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which selector is used to target an element based on its id?',
      options: ['#id','.id','*id','id'],
      answer: '#id',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the universal selector (*) do in CSS?',
      options: ['Targets all elements in a document','Targets no elements','Targets the body element','Targets elements with a specific id'],
      answer: 'Targets all elements in a document',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the correct syntax to select all <p> elements inside <div> elements?',
      options: ['div p','div + p','div > p','p > div'],
      answer: 'div p',
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is true about the CSS selector div.example?',
        options: ['Selects all divs with the class "example"',' Selects the first div with the class "example"','Selects all divs','Selects all elements with the class "example"'],
        answer: 'Selects all divs with the class "example"',
      },
      {
        question: 'Identify the error in the CSS code: .class { color: blue; font-weight; bold; }',
        options: ['Syntax error in property declaration',' Missing class name',' Incorrect property value','No error'],
        answer: 'Syntax error in property declaration',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following property is used as shorthand to specify a number of other font properties?',
        options: [' font-size','font','font-variant','font-weight'],
        answer: 'font',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following property is used to set the width of an image?',
        options: [' border','height','width','-moz-opacity'],
        answer: 'width',
      }
  ];
  
